Support for NPR Music comes from Capital
NPR Music 得到了 Capital
One, proud supporters of NPR Music and
One 的支持，Capital One 是 NPR Music 和
the Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
Tiny Desk Contest 的忠实支持者。 你的钱包里有什么
wallet? Learn more at capitalone.com.
？ 了解更多信息，请访问 capitalone.com。
&gt;&gt; And the band is the Space Age Pimps.
乐队的名字是太空时代皮条客乐队。
&gt;&gt; Space Age Pimps.
太空时代的皮条客。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 是的
We are witnessing
我们正在见证
Space Age Pimps.
太空时代的皮条客。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Oh, [music] yeah.
哦，[音乐]是的。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Go.
开始。
Hard with [music] the gangster [singing]
伴着音乐，匪帮成员唱着歌，
lean, gold smile for the women that be
瘦削的身躯，金色的笑容，献给那些
jocking the green. I'm a pimpster, not a
追逐金钱的女人。 我是个皮条客，不是
trick [singing and music] on the stroll.
街头卖淫的[唱歌跳舞]。
You got to pimp that thing and keep a
你得好好炫耀一下那玩意儿，还得留着个
trick on hold. Stay on top of the
妞儿伺候它。
[music] world with a gun in [singing]
手握枪支，边唱歌边称霸乐坛
your hand. Take control of a woman, fear
。 掌控女人，
no man. It be hard for me to see a day
无惧男人。 我很难想象
without cash. [music and singing] If you
没有现金的日子。  [音乐和歌唱] 如果你
got it and I don't, I'll blast your ass
有而我没有，我会迅速干掉你，
with the quickness because a [singing]
因为[唱歌的]
pimp don't play. I got to work on my
皮条客可不是闹着玩的。 我得开始研究我的
[music] game, think of ways to get paid.
音乐事业，想想怎么赚钱。
Born in the mound down deep in the south
出生在南方深处的土堆里，
with the brothers with the curls and
和那两个有着卷发和
gold teeth in their mouth. In this
金牙的兄弟一起生活。 在这辆
Chevrolet [music] Impalas with the
雪佛兰[音乐] Impala里，有
crackers and Vogues. Vogue deep with the
饼干和Vogue。  Vogue杂志深入报道了
yak smoking fat mackin' dough. Fall up
牦牛抽着肥肉的美味。
in the club with the pimpster tone.
用皮条客的语气在夜店里招摇过市。
[music] Got a check in my pants. You
[音乐] 我裤子里揣着一张支票。 你
step to me in this zone. Got a family in
在这片区域向我走来。 在孟菲斯有家人
Memphis, gang [music] in Texas, T-Money
，在德州搞帮派音乐，T-Money
in the Jag, JB [singing] in the Lexus,
开捷豹，JB 开雷克萨斯唱歌，
Texas. Pimp tight mind in the studio
德州。 录音棚四号的皮条客思维很紧
four.
。
I'm coming out hard.
我要强势出击。
What we doing? What [music] we doing? We
我们在做什么？ 我们正在创作什么音乐？ 我们要全力以赴
coming out hard.
。
What we doing? What we doing?
我们在做什么？ 我们在做什么？
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; We coming out hard.
我们强势回归。
What we doing? [music] What we doing? We
我们在做什么？  [音乐] 我们在做什么？ 我们要全力以赴
coming out hard.
。
&gt;&gt; I am J G, description of brother and one
我是 J G，一个哥哥，一个
who tends to always keep his business
总是把自己的生意
under cover. But still I wind up in the
隐藏起来的人。 但我仍然会在
[singing and music] middle of a click.
唱歌和音乐的间隙中沉浸其中。
Somebody heard, he heard, she heard.
有人听到了，他听到了，她也听到了。
Should I continue to listen to the
我该继续听信那些
rumors, [music] the garbage? Trick I
谣言、那些垃圾音乐吗？ 骗子，我才
ain't buying this sucker. Let's start
不信这鬼东西。 让我们开始
this rumble. Swing, trick. You miss, I
这场混战吧。 摇摆，技巧。 你没打中，我
hit, tumble into the speaker. [music]
打中，然后撞到音箱上。  [音乐]
Now [singing] you're feeling weaker.
现在 [歌唱] 你感觉越来越虚弱了。
Man, don't step when you think you got
伙计，别以为自己已经
back up. [music] Looking for some
重新站起来了，否则就大错特错了。  [音乐] 想找人
[singing] help, but your boys just
帮忙唱歌，但你们的伙计们都
slacked up. Pumped up, got back, laid
偷懒了。 精神抖擞，回到家，
low, [music] headed to the front door.
低调行事，[音乐]走向前门。
Sneaking out real slow. How you feel
偷偷溜出去，慢慢地。 你现在感觉如何
now? What's wrong? What's the matter?
？ 怎么了？ 怎么了？
[music] Hey, mama never told you not to
[音乐] 嘿，妈妈可没告诉你不要把
baby those rhymes. Him, J G got juice in
那些童谣当儿歌念。 他，J G 在 92 中表现出色
the 9 deuce. What? [music] For the 9 tre
。 什么？  [音乐] 为9特雷
bill. Don't play with. I'mma stay true.
法案。 不要玩弄。 我会始终如一。
Some of y'all going trade. [music] Some
你们有些人要去交易。  [音乐]
of y'all love my life. Some of y'all
你们有些人喜欢我的生活。 我知道你们有些人
going hate, but see I'm in it to win it.
会恨我，但你要知道，我参赛就是为了赢。   我
Not in it for a part and it's considered
不是来凑热闹的，而且
hard for me to come out damn hard.
对我来说，要表现得非常强硬也很难。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; What we doing? What we doing? We [music]
我们在做什么？ 我们在做什么？ 我们（音乐）
coming out hard.
强势回归。
What we doing? What we doing? We coming
我们在做什么？ 我们在做什么？ 我们要全力以赴
out hard.
。
&gt;&gt; [music and singing]
[音乐和歌唱]
&gt;&gt; What we doing? What we doing? We coming
我们在做什么？ 我们在做什么？ 我们要全力以赴
out hard.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Coming out hard.
。 是的。 是的。 强势出击。
Coming [music] out hard.
强势出击（音乐）。
Coming out hard.
强势出击。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; What we doing? What we doing? We coming
我们在做什么？ 我们在做什么？ 我们要全力以赴
out hard.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I'm a push.
我是推动者。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; From the first album coming out hard, if
不管
you didn't know that or not.
你知不知道，他们的第一张专辑一经推出就势头强劲。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声] 是
&gt;&gt; Yeah, yeah, man. Appreciate the love,
啊，是啊，伙计。 感谢
y'all. That
大家的喜爱。 这
that song is older than
首歌的年龄
is possibly some people in this room.
可能比在座某些人的年龄还要大。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; Straight up.
没错。
&gt;&gt; It's a whole daddy old, that's what we
它已经老得不行了，我们都这么
call it.
叫它。
You know,
你知道，
or a whole mama old, you know, whatever
或者说，一个老妈妈，你知道，随便
you want to call it.
你怎么称呼它。   是啊
&gt;&gt; Yeah, man, yeah.
，没错。
What we doing?
我们在做什么？
&gt;&gt; 1 2
1 2
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱] 我
&gt;&gt; Said I got the blues.
说我得了忧郁症。   我
Said I got [music] the blues.
说我得了（音乐）忧郁症。
The Memphis City blues.
孟菲斯之城的蓝调。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。   是的
Yeah. Light up the green, watch me light
。 点亮绿色灯光，看我点亮整个
up the room, watch me light up the mic.
房间，看我点燃麦克风。
Fat boy be the truth. [__] live
胖子说的是实话。 黑鬼
[singing] and learn. Learn the streets
边唱边学。 了解
of the burn. [__] take what you earn.
燃烧的街道。 那些家伙会抢走你挣来的东西。
They be slick as a perm. Man, I try to
它们光滑得像烫过的头发一样。 伙计，我努力让自己
[singing] be slicker. Try to be cunning
唱歌更流畅一些。 尽量狡猾，动作
and quicker. [music] Try to be more than
更快。  [音乐]
just another broke ass [__] in this
在这场
game of life. Lose your life in the
人生游戏中，努力让自己不仅仅是另一个穷光蛋。 在游戏中失去生命
game.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Take a life full of pain, make [singing]
经历充满痛苦的一生，[歌唱] 让
you remember my name. From the home of
你记住我的名字。 来自
the blues. Thought I paid my dues. It's
蓝调音乐的故乡。 我以为我已经付出了代价。
hard to fill my shoes. In what haters
我的位置很难有人能取代。 被仇恨者
abuse. [music and singing]
滥用。  [音乐和歌唱]
I just love the music like my heart and
我热爱音乐，就像热爱我的心和
my brain. Couldn't live without it.
我的大脑一样。 没有它我活不下去。
That's impossible, man. I'm unstoppable,
那不可能，老兄。 我势不可挡，
[singing]
[唱歌的]
man. From [music] the bottom I came.
人。 我从音乐的底层一路走来。   那些为了生计
[__] scratching for bread, stumbled up
奔波的黑人，误打误撞地
on the fame. Humble [__] [music] with
成名了。 谦逊的黑人[音乐]有
game. Shut your mouth up and listen.
实力。 闭嘴听着。
Recognize it's a blessing. Thankful just
要认识到这是一种恩赐。
to be [music] living. I got the Memphis
能够以音乐为生，我感到无比感恩。 我得了孟菲斯
City blues.
蓝调症。
Ooh, I can feel it. The neighborhood
哦，我能感觉到。 街区里的
pimps introduced us to pimping. And
皮条客把我们带入了皮条客的世界。
everybody [music] we know used to play
我们认识的所有音乐家都曾
in them streets. So, man, oh man, oh
在街头演奏过。 唉，唉，唉
man, I got them Memphis city blues. I
，我得了孟菲斯蓝调。 我
can [music and singing] feel it. The
能感受到（音乐和歌声）。
neighborhood cousins introduced us to
邻居表兄弟们带我们接触了
pimpin' and everybody we know used to
皮条客文化，我们认识的每个人都曾经
play in them streets. So, man, oh man,
在街头混过。 所以，老兄，哦，老兄，
oh man, I had them Memphis city soul
哦，老兄，早在八口之家还挤在一楼的时候，我的骨头里就流淌着孟菲斯城的灵魂乐
people was in grade homes. Even further
。 更早
back when I was just playing up in my
以前，我还在自家
yard, ride [music and singing] biting
院子里玩耍，骑着摩托车（听着音乐唱歌），
in the music city, Memphis 10. It turned
在音乐之城孟菲斯摸爬滚打，练就了一身本领。这让
me into [singing] this. My dad and a
我变成了现在这样（唱歌）。 我爸爸和
couple [music] of my friends, they
我几个朋友都会
played instruments. And when we used to
演奏乐器。
roll to school at 16, I bumped [__] like
16岁的时候，我们开车去上学，我经常听
Bobby Womack and Al Green. Hell, [music]
鲍比·沃马克和艾尔·格林之类的歌。 说真的，[音乐]
I knew most of the old school [__] from
我对大多数老派音乐都了如指掌
front to end. I was starting to memorize
。 我十岁就开始背诵
four fives at age 10. I come [music]
四个五拍子了。我
from a city where R&amp;B run deep and the
来自一个 R&amp;B 音乐氛围浓厚的城市，
blues was the music that paved the whole
蓝调音乐是那里的主要音乐
street. It was only natural that
。
[music and singing] we would take the
我们接过
torch and run with it. Be serious but
火炬，继续发扬光大，这是理所当然的。 认真对待
still have a little fun [music] with it.
音乐，但也要从中获得一些乐趣。
MJG from a town that run real deep. Ask
MJG来自一个底蕴深厚的城镇。
B.B. King and Isaac Hayes on Beale
去比尔街问问 B.B. King 和 Isaac Hayes 吧
[music] Street. I got them Memphis city
。 我让他们得了孟菲斯
blues. I can feel [singing] it. The
蓝调。 我能感受到（唱歌的时候）。
neighborhood cousins introduced us to
邻居表兄弟们带我们接触了
pimpin'
街头
&gt;&gt; [music]
音乐，
&gt;&gt; and everybody we know used to play in
我们认识的每个人都曾在
them streets. So, man, oh man, oh man, I
街头演奏过。 所以，老兄，哦，老兄，哦，老兄，我
got them [music] Memphis city blues. I
得了孟菲斯蓝调音乐。 我
can feel it.
能感觉到。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; The neighborhood cousins introduced us
街坊邻居的表兄弟们带我们入了
to pimpin' and everybody we know used to
皮条客的圈子，我们认识的每个人都曾经
play in them streets. So, man,
在街头混过。 所以，伙计，
[music and singing] oh man, oh man.
（音乐和歌声）哦，伙计，哦，伙计。
Ooh.
哦。
Take it on home, Mar. What we doing?
把东西带回家吧，玛尔。我们这是在干什么？
&gt;&gt; I [music] got them Memphis city
我（音乐）让他们孟菲斯城
&gt;&gt; [music]
（音乐）
&gt;&gt; Tony Gentry on the wire, y'all. Tony
托尼·根特里在线，伙计们。 托尼·
Gentry on the wire.
根特里在电波中。
&gt;&gt; Memphis city blues.
孟菲斯城市蓝调。
Ooh.
哦。
&gt;&gt; Memphis City Blues
孟菲斯城市蓝调
&gt;&gt; [applause and cheering]
[掌声和欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; That's our Memphis City Blues. That's
这就是我们的孟菲斯城市蓝调。
off the Living Legends album, I believe,
我记得这首歌好像是出自《Living Legends》专辑
man.
。
That was our first album with Bad Boy,
那是我们和 Bad Boy 合作的第一张专辑
man. Uh
。 啊，真是
beautiful time, man. Beautiful time,
美好的时光啊。 美好的时光啊，
man.
伙计。
that that that song is organic. It
那首歌是自然而然的。 它
really
真实地
tells of the music history and the
讲述了我们城市——田纳西州孟菲斯的音乐历史和
musical influence from our city,
音乐影响
Memphis, Tennessee.
。
&gt;&gt; Definitely. The home of the blues, man.
确实。 这里是蓝调音乐的故乡，老兄。
It's also the home of this type of
这里也是这类
stuff, too.
东西的聚集地。
&gt;&gt; Straight [music] from the underground.
来自地下音乐的纯粹之作。
Bad boy from the mouth, spit it. How I
嘴上说出来，别装坏小子。 我的
live it. Keep it gutter, that's [music]
生活方式。 保持这种接地气的风格，这就是
how we get down. I want to see you get
我们玩音乐的方式。 我想看到你明白
it, crumb. Let a [__] know what hood
，小家伙。 让别人知道
you from. Everybody with me drunk as
你来自哪个街区。 我身边的人都喝得
[__] Break it down. Roll it up. Bag
烂醉。 分解一下。 卷起来。 把
[music] it up. A girl like you, a [__]
音乐装进​​袋子里。 像你这样的女孩，
like me can't handle it. Roll in back,
像我这样的男孩，都应付不了。 滚到后面，
looking good. Put it in a verse. Bag it
看起来不错。 把它写成一首诗。 把
[music] up. What's the deal? Let me make
音乐打包起来。 到底是怎么回事？ 让我
it clear. What you got right here, they
把话说清楚。 你看到的这款产品，他们
broke the mold. One of a kind. Bad
打破了常规。 独一无二。 坏
[music] boy with a gold mouth, that's
男孩（音乐）嘴里含着金牙，时候到了
time. Hard to tell. Probably tell these
。 很难说。 可能会告诉这些
boys out here ain't hard as us. Ball and
小伙子们，他们没我们这么厉害。  Ball 和
G, hard as street. Hardest street are
G，硬汉，街头范儿十足。 最艰难的街头
part [music] of us. Lay it down. Please
音乐也是我们的一部分。 把它放下。 请
remember gangs, we don't play them now.
记住，我们现在不跟帮派玩了。   别
Disrespect, please remember [music]
不尊重人，请记住[音乐]里的
things we don't we don't bust a [__]
事，我们不会打爆黑人的
head, smack a hoe, shoot the club up.
头，不会打女人，也不会在夜店里开枪。
Bust a [__] head, a hoe.
打爆黑鬼的头，还有婊子的头。
Shoot the club, uh.
射击俱乐部，呃。
&gt;&gt; [__]
婊子
[__] [music]
黑鬼。  [音乐]
&gt;&gt; [__] [__]
婊子黑鬼。
&gt;&gt; You don't
你不想
to go.
去。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; You
你
don't
不想
to go.
去。
You
你
don't
不想让
want
音乐
&gt;&gt; [music]
消失。
You
你
don't
不想
to go. Let's go.
去。 我们走吧。
Hold up.
耽误。
Who? Hold up.
WHO？ 耽误。
Who? You going [music] to have to break
WHO？ 你得把这音乐拆解
this thing down.
开来。
Who?
WHO？
&gt;&gt; make Don't make me kill me kill no
WHO？   别逼
[__] [music] body in here or in
他妈的不会杀任何人。[音乐] 身体在这里或这里
here. I'mma shoot I'mma shoot three
。 我要开枪，我要开三
shots three shots. Somebody done
枪，三枪。 有人让
made me hot.
我感到燥热。
&gt;&gt; One more time.
再一次。
&gt;&gt; Don't make Don't make me kill me
别逼我杀人，别逼我
kill no [__] body in here or in
杀这里或这里面的任何一个人
here. I'mma shoot I'mma shoot three
。 我要开枪，我要开三
[music] shots three shots. Somebody done
枪（音乐），三枪。 有人让
made me hot.
我感到燥热。
&gt;&gt; Hot.
热的。
&gt;&gt; You got me [__] up. We shoot guns in
你把我搞糊涂了。 我们在
here, target meet market. Y'all haters
这里射击，瞄准目标市场。 你们这些
up who start [__] Hill J, G R.I.P.
挑事儿的喷子都给我闭嘴。  Hill J, G 安息
Pooh. Bodyguards out [music] of line,
呸。 保镖已撤离（音乐），
police is in order. Thought they bought
警察已就位。 以为他们真的被
it hard that when the party started.
派对开始了。   我
Thought we was all chilling, I figured
以为大家都在放松休息，我以为
that everybody be leaving here all
大家都会离开这里，全部
leaving. You standing too close, [__]
离开。 你站得太近了，黑鬼。
You asking too much, baby.
宝贝，你要求太多了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; It may need [__] coming around
也许需要一些黑人过来
talking about they hot, but they not.
谈论他们有多性感，但他们并不性感。
[__] them with Bad Boy and MJ, [__]
去他妈的，跟Bad Boy和MJ比，黑鬼，
we the two truth. Holler at a player man
我们才是真理。 在游戏
streets of the booth. We popping at them
亭的街道上向玩家大喊。 我们用
[music] haters man soft and [__] make
音乐狠狠打击那些讨厌我们的人，让他们这些软蛋和黑鬼
they chin hit the floor. Then all red
哑口无言。 然后所有红
[__] take they [music] cheese and
黑帮都拿走了他们的[音乐]奶酪，
they whole mafia.
他们整个黑手党都参与其中。
[__] know
黑鬼们都知道，
&gt;&gt; when the real life [music] films hit the
当现实生活中的[音乐]电影大获成功的时候
dough. Come on.
。 快点。
&gt;&gt; Come on.
快点。
&gt;&gt; Don't make Don't make me kill me kill no
别逼我杀人，别逼我杀
[__] body in here or in
这里或这里面的任何一个人
here. I'mma shoot I'mma shoot three
。 我要开枪，我要开三
shots
枪，
Somebody done made me hot. Don't make me
有人惹我生气了。 别逼我（用
&gt;&gt; [music]
音乐）
in here.
在这里杀人。
I'm a shoot
我打算开
three shots.
三枪。
Somebody
有人让
done made me
我感到
hot.
燥热。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; We just having fun.
我们只是在玩而已。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; Just having fun. We're just in the nest.
只是玩玩而已。 我们只是在巢里。
I wish we could go loud. But
我希望我们能大声喊叫。 但
&gt;&gt; Louder.
声音更大。
&gt;&gt; It is all good, man. We just tiny
一切都好，伙计。 我们只是把它放在一张小
desking it.
桌子上。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; You know, hey. That was a Living Legend
你知道，嘿。 那也是一张堪称“活着的传奇”的
album as well, man. Living Legend album
专辑，真的。  《活着的传奇》专辑，
just for the people, you know, in uh the
专为
internet world. The the youngins who
互联网世界的人们而作。 那些
don't know. So, y'all can go boom boom
不懂事的年轻人。 所以，你们可以四处搜寻，
and find us.
找到我们。
&gt;&gt; The Living Legends album.
《活着的传奇》专辑。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Let's do another one from that
。 我们再来一首那张
album.
专辑里的歌吧。
&gt;&gt; One.
一。
Two.
二。
Three.
三。
Four.
四、
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Push.
推。
&gt;&gt; See a real [__] like me got to get
像我这样的真男人，就得努力
money till I get rich. Ride with a
赚钱，直到发财致富。 带着
couple hundred Gs in the biscuit. Down
几百G的重力加速度骑行。 随便听听
[music] for whatever. Hustling with my
音乐。 和我的
misfit home. [singing]
格格不入的家一起奋斗。  [唱歌]
So, you going to see how [__] this
所以，
might be once [music] we get rich. Till
一旦我们[靠音乐]发财了，你们就会明白这有多糟糕了。 在此之前
then, it's back to hustling with my
，我得继续和我的那些
[singing] misfits. Deep on the creep.
（唱歌的）怪咖们一起奔波了。 悄悄地爬得很深。
Fifty zones on under the brawl.
混战之下有五十个区域。
Fifty zones on
五十个区域，
I keep a big old [__] beater heater.
我带着一把老式大黑鬼牌电枪。
It's in the trunk. On [music] my photo
它在后备箱里。 关于[音乐]我的照片
and my duke. See the make
和我的公爵。 看看我如何化解危机
skin up, skin up, give up and grab the
，化解危机，放弃抵抗，然后像
ball back just like I'm Barry Cheetah. I
巴里·猎豹一样重新夺回球权。 我
know you want to [__] my hole but you
知道你想操我的屁眼，但你又
too scared to meet her.
太害怕见她。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 你
&gt;&gt; See, you ain't got enough bread to even
看，你连给
start to treat her. The way I've been
她治病的钱都没有。 我一直以来都是这样，
did and in the bed I'm even sweeter. I
在床上我更是温柔体贴。 我
hustle,
努力奋斗，
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I got more Franklins than Anita Baker.
我赚的钱比安妮塔·贝克还多。
If I had a Oprah Winfrey, I would marry
如果我有一个像奥普拉·温弗瑞那样的人，我会娶
[music] her and keep her. I spit this
她为妻，永远和她在一起。 我传播这些
knowledge and preach this and teach this
知识，宣扬这些知识，教导这些知识，
just as long the message [music]
只要信息（音乐）能够
reaches, we all fill up the breaches.
传播出去，我们就能填补空白。
I'm the L J
我是L J，
I get in your [__] [music] I ain't
我会搞砸你的烂摊子。  [音乐] 我不想
and be your friend so quick. I'm on that
那么快就融入你的小圈子，和你成为朋友。 我的
wave, my money. Let me hit the [music]
钱也投在了这波浪潮上。 让我登上音乐
stage. [__] them long interviews, just
舞台吧。 别搞那些冗长的采访了，直接
give us the front page. Black apostrophe
给我们头版就行。 黑色撇号
[music] S, us forever bust. Give lyrics
[音乐] S，我们永远失败。 写出
that make the people say that he got
让人觉得他
nothing on
在音乐方面一无是处的歌词。
&gt;&gt; What we going to [music and singing] do,
我们接下来要做什么呢
man?
？
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱]
bronze?
青铜之下有多少关节？
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Appreciate the love, y'all. Appreciate
感谢大家的喜爱。 感谢你的
the love, man. Appreciate the love.
爱，兄弟。 感谢这份爱。
Thank you very much. It's a blessing to
非常感谢。
be here today, man. It's a blessing to
今天能来到这里真是我的荣幸。
be here today.
今天能来到这里，我感到非常荣幸。
Um
嗯，
A lot of years, y'all. A lot of years.
很多年了，各位。 很多年了。
It's a blessing.
这是件好事。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yes.
。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yes, it is. It It's definitely is.
，确实如此。 确实如此。
&gt;&gt; You know, y'all uh
你们都知道，要
Cherish every day. Cherish every day
珍惜每一天。 珍惜与亲人相处的每一天
your loved ones.
。
Tell them you love them every day. You
每天都告诉他们你爱他们。 你
hear me, man?
听见了吗，伙计？
&gt;&gt; You never know.
谁也说不准。
&gt;&gt; Straight up.
直截了当。
&gt;&gt; Check on that person when you leave
你离开这里的时候记得去看看那个人
here.
。
&gt;&gt; Facts. Facts. Facts.
事实。 事实。 事实。
&gt;&gt; All right.
好的。   开始吧
&gt;&gt; Let's get it.
。
Jump in the Cadillac.
跳进凯迪拉克。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Uh.
嗯。
Take it [music] back. Yeah.
把音乐收回去。 是的。
I'll be your blast if you step outside
如果你走出去，我会让你嗨翻天，
because [music] my ride is awaiting. A
因为[音乐]我的车正在等你。 一次
date, a steak, a nightcap. We mated,
约会，一份牛排，一杯睡前酒。 我们交合了，
awoken by smells of perfume
被香水味
[music and singing] that I inhale and
（音乐和歌声）唤醒，我吸入这些味道，
then tell her well we raise hell on the
然后告诉她，我们在
des- satin sheets. [music and singing]
缎面床单上尽情狂欢。  [音乐和歌声]
Heat from your feet keep me warm. The
你脚底的热量让我感到温暖。
the [music and singing] storm. You came
音乐和歌声如同暴风雨般袭来，将气氛烘托得淋漓尽致。 你来势
strong but I lasted longer than I ever
汹汹，但我坚持的时间比以往任何时候都长
lasted.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Your mouth was fantastic. The [__] test
你的嘴太棒了。
you passed it. In a way you made a
你通过了那该死的测试。 从某种意义上说，你
[__] laugh. I had to get you. And when
逗笑了一个黑鬼。 我必须找到你。 当
I saw that ass pass, I had [music] to
我看到那屁股经过时，我真想放首歌
hit you. You're making me fight against
揍你。 你这是在逼我违背自己的
my will. What must I do now? Would you
意愿去战斗。 我现在该怎么办？ 你愿意
kill for me? Yeah. If [music] my life's
为我杀人吗？ 是的。 如果音乐也危及我的生命，那我的生命也会受到
in danger, too. Would you steal for me?
威胁。 你愿意为我偷东西吗？   是的
Yeah. If this [__] belongs to you, here
。 如果这东西是你的，请你替
and feel for me. Yeah. If the way you
我感到难过。 是的。 如果你的
act is true, who knows? [singing] Fine
行为是真诚的，谁知道呢？  [唱歌] 漂亮的
clothes. Lexus doors [music] you'll be
衣服。 雷克萨斯车门 [音乐]
closing when you become one of the
当你成为被选中的人之一时，你会关上它，
chosen you holding different places,
你拥有不同的地方、
different faces, different cases. They
不同的面孔、不同的境遇。 他们
got me tired [music and singing] like
（音乐和歌声）让我感到疲惫，就像
shoelaces but no mistake is MJG you
鞋带一样，但毫无疑问，MJG 你
ain't got a beat. Constantly trying to
没有节奏。 不断试图
shoot that P claiming that you ain't
攻击那个P，声称你没听
heard of me. Giving it real, let me know
说过我。 说实话，告诉我
how you feel. When we communicate,
你的感受。 当我们交流时，
[singing]
（唱歌）
we'll be straight if you express your
如果你能表达你的
[music] mind instead of preferring to
（音乐）想法而不是选择
wait. Now some who can't do it, they
等待，我们会直截了当地交流。 现在，有些做不到这一点的人，就会
lose women. But [__] like me used to
失去女人。 但像我这样的黑鬼早就习惯了
it. Face says [music] paper. Let's go.
。 脸说[乐谱]纸。 我们走吧。
&gt;&gt; You came. You
你来了。 你
came. Once in a while.
来了。 偶尔。
&gt;&gt; this [music] is how we play.
这就是我们的演奏方式。
&gt;&gt; This ain't nothing but a thug thing.
这纯粹是流氓行径。
[singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Nothing is too strong.
没有什么是太强的。
&gt;&gt; This ain't nothing [singing and music]
这根本不是什么歌唱和音乐，
but a thug
而是一个恶棍
Setting out in all of
在
the city lights and sounds.
城市的灯光和喧嚣中横行霸道。
&gt;&gt; [music and singing]
[音乐和歌唱]
&gt;&gt; Talk [music] to you, and I,
和你和我谈[音乐]，
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[歌唱]
&gt;&gt; me and you. Situation getting sticky.
你和我。 情况变得棘手了。
Your mouth is saying [music] no, but
你的嘴巴在说[音乐]不，但
your body is saying "Stick me, lick me."
你的身体却在说“粘住我，舔我”。
Don't be afraid of what your friends
不要害怕朋友
say. [singing and music] Rappers get
说什么。  [歌唱和音乐] 说唱歌手们搞到手
that ass, then be out of here like
后，就赶紧滚蛋，就像
yesterday. But not tonight. You look so
昨天一样。 但今晚不行。 你看起来身材
tight, it feels so right. [music] This
真好，感觉很对。  [音乐] 这
endo got me perved. Let's go [singing]
内窥镜让我色眯眯的。 让我们出发吧 [唱歌]
hop in my 'Burb and ride till we get to
跳上我的雪佛兰Suburban，一路开到
where you want to be, no matter how far.
你想去的地方，无论多远。
Just call [music] me ball, baby. To me,
宝贝，就叫我[音乐]球吧。 在我眼里，
you're the superstar. Ask me time and
你就是超级巨星。 一遍又一遍地问我
time again [singing] why did I choose
（唱）我为什么选择
you? Do I want to [music] be your man or
你？ 我想让音乐成为你的男人，还是
just misuse you? I hear your partner
只想利用你？ 我听到你的伴侣在背后
dissing [singing] when they think I
唱着歌，以为我
ain't listening. Them hoes just be
没在听。 那些婊子们肯定巴不得
wishing they could be in your position.
自己能站在你这个位置上。
[music] With me and luxury, I got to be.
[音乐] 对我来说，奢华是必不可少的。
Chiefing hay with some stout, wearing
一边喝着烈酒，一边穿着
[music] lingerie. Let's hit the tail,
音乐主题的性感内衣，吃着干草。 让我们去船尾，
[singing] get a suite, order something
[唱]订个套房，点些
to eat. Tell me [__] about you, I'll
吃的。 告诉我你的坏话，我也会
tell you [__] about [music] me. Then out
告诉你我的音乐。 然后
the blue, I'll be caressing you,
，我会突然抚摸你，
undressing you. You start doing
脱掉你的衣服。 你开始做
[music and singing] all that [__] you
你以前说过永远不会做的事（音乐和唱歌）
said you'd never do. Lusting, busting,
。 欲望涌上心头，
all out of my boxer drawers. Fingers
我的内裤都快要撑破了。 手指
slipping, sliding [singing] in and out,
滑进滑出，
and in and out. Constantly [music]
进进出出。 音乐不断地
telling me the things you don't do. Yet
告诉我你不会做的事情。 但
you [singing] do it like a pro and think
你唱歌唱得像个专业人士，却以为
that I don't know. But I do. [music]
我不懂。 但我确实有。  [音乐]
That's why I'm here with you, and you
这就是我来这里陪你的原因，你也
know this. Slip on the latex [singing]
知道这一点。 穿上乳胶衣[唱歌]，
and dive in.
纵身跃入。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]我们
&gt;&gt; Every once in a while, this is how we
偶尔就是这样
play.
玩耍的。
&gt;&gt; This ain't nothing [singing] but a
这不算什么（唱歌），但“
&gt;&gt; Nothing is too strong.
什么都不是”这个词太强烈了。
&gt;&gt; This ain't nothing but a
这不过是……
&gt;&gt; We're sitting
我们
out in all of the
坐在城市灯光下
&gt;&gt; [singing]
（唱歌），这
&gt;&gt; city lights
不过是……
&gt;&gt; Just sitting in all of
只是坐在……
It's ain't nothing but a
这不过是……这不过是（音乐）这不过是
&gt;&gt; [screaming]
（尖叫）
&gt;&gt; [music]
（音乐）
&gt;&gt; It's ain't nothing
这不过是……
Yeah.
耶。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; It's ain't nothing but a
这不过是
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
耶。
They say it counts.
他们说这很重要。
We love y'all.
我们爱你们。
Hey.
嘿。
Already thank y'all again, man.
再次感谢各位！   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; Thank y'all. [cheering]
谢谢大家。  [欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; [applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank y'all. Thank y'all. We appreciate
谢谢大家。 谢谢大家。 我们感谢大家的
the love.
喜爱。
&gt;&gt; y'all.
你们。
&gt;&gt; Everybody in the band, Mar.
乐队里的每个人，Mar。
&gt;&gt; Everybody.
每个人。
&gt;&gt; Keyel.
凯尔。
Tony.
托尼。
Doc.
医生。
Los on the drums. DJ Tail.
Los担任鼓手。  DJ Tail。
&gt;&gt; Good job.
好工作。
&gt;&gt; Marcus over here, man.
马库斯在这儿呢，伙计。
&gt;&gt; I don't play no [music] games.
我不玩任何音乐游戏。
&gt;&gt; Coffee team, Push Management.
咖啡团队，Push Management。
&gt;&gt; Peace out of Space Age Films.
太空时代电影公司再见。
&gt;&gt; The Space Age Films behind us. Push
我们身后的是太空时代电影。 推送
Management. Tiny Desk. [music]
管理。 迷你办公桌。  [音乐]
Everybody, man. Thank y'all.
大家，伙计们。 谢谢大家。
&gt;&gt; y'all.
你们。
&gt;&gt; Appreciate [singing] the love, man.
欣赏歌声中的爱吧，兄弟。
My son laying here, man. My older son,
我儿子躺在这里，唉。 我的大儿子，
man. Love you, man. You get to see this,
伙计。 兄弟，我爱你。 伙计，你能看到这个
man. Yeah.
。 是的。
But, thank y'all, man. [music] We
但是，谢谢大家。  [音乐] 我们
appreciate the [singing] love. Y'all go
感谢[歌唱]的喜爱。 各位，
home safe, man.
一路平安。
&gt;&gt; Thank y'all.
谢谢大家。
&gt;&gt; Love somebody.
爱上某人。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Let's drink some coffee, man. Let's
咱们喝点咖啡吧，伙计。 咱们
drink some coffee, man.
喝点咖啡吧，伙计。
Let's drink some coffee, man.
咱们喝点咖啡吧，伙计。
Google that. Google that.
谷歌一下。 谷歌一下。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢。 谢谢。 谢谢。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause and cheering]
[掌声和欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; Appreciate y'all, man. Thank you.
谢谢大家，伙计们。 谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Thank you for the love.
感谢大家的喜爱。
&gt;&gt; Appreciate it, man.
谢谢啦，兄弟。
&gt;&gt; Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
感谢观看。  NPR
Music comes from Rivian, makers of
Music 得到了 Rivian 的支持，Rivian 是一家生产
all-electric adventure vehicles designed
全电动探险车的公司，其设计充分考虑了
with the planet and future generations
地球和子孙后代的福祉
in mind.
。
A quick update before you go. We're
临走前简单汇报一下情况。 我们将
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
再次举办 Tiny Desk 赠送活动。 参加截止日期
by September 12th, [music] 2026, and you
为 2026 年 9 月 12 日，你
and a friend could win a free trip to DC
和你的朋友就有机会赢得前往华盛顿特区的免费旅行，亲临
to see a Tiny Desk concert live in
现场观看 Tiny Desk 音乐会
person. You even get [music] to choose
。 你甚至可以通过音乐来选择
which upcoming show you want to see, and
你想观看的即将上映的节目，而且
it's completely free to enter. Just go
完全免费参加。 请访问
to npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway。
Entering is completely free, but you can
参赛完全免费，但您可以
get more entries by snagging some
通过购买
limited edition Tiny Desk merch or by
限量版 Tiny Desk 周边商品或
making a special donation [music] to the
向
NPR network. Learn more and enter today
NPR 网络捐赠音乐来获得更多参赛机会。 了解更多信息并立即参加，请访问
at npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway。